[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Audrey Hepburn, Jean-Claude Van Damme, Django Reinhardt, Toots Thielemans, and Adolphe Sax were all born in this country.", "correct_answer": "Belgium", "incorrect_answers": ["Luxembourg", "France", "The Netherlands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor, who starred in The Man Who Came Back (2007), also played Chris in Guns of the Magnificent Seven.", "correct_answer": "George Kennedy", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve McQueen", "Peter Graves", "Jim Rockford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what part of the potato is most of its protein located?", "correct_answer": "Just under the skin", "incorrect_answers": ["It is evenly distributed.", "In the skin", "In its center"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many separate rings does the planet Uranus have according to observations made with the Hubble Space Telescope in 2005?", "correct_answer": "13 rings", "incorrect_answers": ["7 rings", "Uranus does not have any rings.", "5 rings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many different chemicals can be found in marijuana?", "correct_answer": "More than 400", "incorrect_answers": ["150", "Less than 5", "200"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following comedies has been on TV the most number of years?", "correct_answer": "The Simpsons", "incorrect_answers": ["Seinfeld", "Ozzie and Harriet", "M*A*S*H"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When is the so-called insurance offered to the player in Blackjack?", "correct_answer": "When the dealers exposed card is an ace", "incorrect_answers": ["When the player has reached 20", "When the dealers exposed card is 10-valued", "When the player has reached 18"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which whale expels a reddish-brown fluid when threatened, much like an octopus?", "correct_answer": "Pygmy sperm whale", "incorrect_answers": ["Dwarf sperm whale", "Andrew\u2019s beaked whale", "Fin whale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jack jumper ants, yellowish-orange carnivorous ants named after their characteristic jumpy motions, can be found only on which continent?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["North America", "Africa", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The clothes that Ice Cube wears in the first scene of the movie Friday are exactly the same as the ones that his character wore in the final scene of Boyz N The Hood.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times did Laurence Fishburne turn down the role of Ike Turner in Whats Love Got to Do With It?", "correct_answer": "Five", "incorrect_answers": ["Two", "Zero", "Seven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long can a goldfish live in optimal conditions?", "correct_answer": "20 years", "incorrect_answers": ["5 years", "8 years", "10 years"]}]